pantel.in 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy

Registration Obligations

“Pantel.in” respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by us. You are advised to please read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy during registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We respect your privacy

At Pantel.in, we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site. 

We want users to:

  * comfortable using our Site.
  * Feel secure in submitting information to us.
  * Know that by using our Site you are consenting to the collection of certain data.

Privacy Guarantee

We promise that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties (except as provided in this Privacy Policy) without your consent. We and/or certain authorized third party service providers will use the personal information provided by you to provide you with the services, which are offered on our portal. From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. 

Information Collectedm

We only collect the details provided by you on registration together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our Site and other sites accessible from them. We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We will collect only such information as is necessary and relevant to us to provide you with the services available on the Site. 

Anonymous Information

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies" sent to your browser from: 

  * web server cookie stored on your hard drive
  * an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use
  * the domain server through which you access our service

Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you like: 

  * name including first and last name
  * mobile phone number and contact details
  * ZIP/Postal code

We use contact information internally to: 

  * direct our efforts for product improvement
  * contact you as a survey respondent
  * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

Our Disclosure of Your Information

We will not use your personal information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. 

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless: 

  * we have your permission
  * to provide products or services you've requested
  * to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of Pantel.in terms of use or to defend against legal claims
  * special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure

Retargeting Privacy Policy   
Steps for user to OPT-OUT of setting website cookie on users browsers 

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies of disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on. 

Information about NPII advertising like behavioural targeting and/or retargeting

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user. 

Steps to OPT-OUT of NPII advertising 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative‘s website by clicking http://www.networkadvertising.org/. 

Security

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate procedures. We will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information; transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

Policy update

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this Site. 

Your Consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

DISCLAIMER

Pantel.IN makes every effort to present accurate and timely information regarding the products we have for sale. However, it is possible that discrepancies or inaccuracies may arise if Pantel.IN receives inaccurate information from our suppliers or other outside sources. Should you encounter any information on our site that you deem inaccurate, please inform us at customercare@Pantel.in 

DISCLAIMERS OF WARRANTIES & PRODUCT LIABILITY

Pantel.in shall not be held liable for any damaged goods or any injuries resulting from use of any products. Pantel.in does not provide warranties on any merchandise--any warranty or promises made by the manufacturers are solely their liability. Many different entities participate in Pantel.in and Pantel.in holds no liability for the services or products sold by them. Pantel.in claims no exclusive ownership of the goods, stores, or services found in this mall, and, as such, Pantel.in shall not be held liable for them. 

The information made available to you through our catalogs is limited to the information provided by the manufacturer to us. All products displayed in our catalogs may not be available for sale due to product unavailability or other reasons. 

Actual colors and dimensions may differ from the screen image of the product. 

INFORMATION LIABILITY

In no event shall Pantel.in or any of its sources be liable for any direct, special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever (including but not limited to: damages for loss of business profits, business interruption, loss of business information, or any other pecuniary loss) arising out of the use of the information made available on this web site. 

Information on the Pantel.in web site may not be reproduced, copied, or altered without the express written consent of Pantel.in and its affiliates. 

Termination

Pantel.in may terminate this Agreement and these terms and conditions and/or the provision of any of the services at any time for any reason, including any improper use of this portal or your failure to comply with these terms and conditions. Such termination shall not affect any right to relief to which Pantel.in and its third party providers and distributors may be entitled, at law or in equity. Upon termination of this User Agreement and these terms and conditions, all rights granted to you will terminate and revert to Pantel.in and its third party providers or distributors, as applicable 

No resale of service

You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service.
